<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">lico-update</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="hello1">Hello Linux User!</string>
    <string name="start1">This app is the official <i>lico-update</i> app of <b>The Linux Counter Project</b>. It will read all needed, system related information from your smartphone and send this information to <b>The Linux Counter Project</b> (https://www.linuxcounter.net). If you do not provide a machine number and an update key for a machine, then it will create a new machine under your LiCo account.</string>
    <string name="start2">Please continue by touching the button below. You then have to enter (or check) your Linux Counter data...</string>
    <string name="button1">Save your Machine-ID\nand Machine UpdateKey\nand get system information</string>
    <string name="button2">Try to send information...</string>
    <string name="button0">Check your machine data...</string>
    <string name="enter_counternum">Please enter the ID of the machine from your profile on https://www.linuxcounter.net.</string>
    <string name="enter_machinenum">Please also enter your machine updatekey. You can see the machine updatekey when visiting your profile on https://www.linuxcounter.net and then clicking on the machine you want to update.</string>
    <string name="enter_updatekey">If you want to update an existing machine and you have entered a machinenumber above, then also enter your update key for this machine here. You can find the update key, when editing the machine on https://www.linuxcounter.net.</string>
    <string name="showdata">The following data will be sent to the Linux Counter if you decide to continue. Please check the data carefully and then confirm sending this data by touching the button below (you may need to scroll).</string>
    <string name="send_data">Send data...</string>
    <string name="sending">Sending...</string>
    <string name="local_service_started">lico-update started!</string>

</resources>
